[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Yonas_p1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What darkness? Corruption?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "No, it was the cold curse of the soulless Lost that brought misery to Brightwood.\\n\\nIf Umberto was even still here by that time, then he may well have departed.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Galahad_p1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm looking for Brother Umberto.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ah, then there may yet be hope! Brother Umberto is a brave soul  - he and I joined forces to defend these fair lands.\\n\\nAh, but the story pains me to speak aloud. It is better if you read the account in my journal, just there.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Galahad_p1_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We could search for Umberto together.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Indeed. I would like nothing more than to find company in this lamentable endeavor.\\n\\nIf you are willing to overlook my failed duties to the Vigil, then I will heartily accept your offer.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Yonas_p3_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What about Brother Umberto?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ser Galahad continues the search in a town just north - the bright knight refuses to believe the Corrupted have again become a greater threat.\\n\\nBut you and I know better, and we cannot simply walk away.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Galahad_p3_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It's a keep known as Caer Dun.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ah, then my suspicions were correct. The fortress of Caer Dun lies some distance from here, however.\\n\\nI will go straightaway, and I will leave you to sort out the truth and the fiction with Yonas. We'll meet again, soon.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Yonas_p5_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What does that mean for us?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "It means the Corrupted have already conquered all the territory from here to the Shattered Mountain. It means we're too late.\\n\\nAny day now, their forces will sweep south and claim the rest of the island.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Grace_p1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So you think the fort is cursed?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "You joking? I already got quite an earful about the curse before I left Calvary.\\n\\nPeople down there don't like to talk about the Bright Vigil, but with a couple of coins, I heard what I needed to hear.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Grace_p1_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I am. What happened to the Bright Vigil?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Well, the dark truth is those righteous bastards turned on each other, and then of course, they all fell Lost.\\n\\nMayor Pennyfather in Calvary - he knows more than he lets on. Lean on him a bit, and he'll cough it up.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Pennyfather_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Because you're hiding something?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Preposterous! I've nothing to hide… I just don't recall all the gory details. I was busy building this town when the Bright Vigil fell.\\n\\nBesides, dredging up such dark affairs serves no purpose. It's just… depressing!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Pennyfather_03",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"But you knew… and did nothing.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, I-I knew what they planned… but if I spoke out, Umberto said he'd bury me too!\\n\\nEvery day, I live with the shame of my silence… and in the time since, I promise, I've done all I can to remove the curse.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Sun_p1_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You're studying the curse on Brightwood?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "He told you? Well then, a secret no more! So yes, I'm trying to restore the \"bright\" to Brightwood.\\n\\nDespite Pennyfather's hopes, restoring the entire forest is impossible, but I might be able to heal some locations.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Galahad_p5_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm meeting Alchemist Sun to the south.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Of course. With so many leads to follow, it's good we can split up.\\n\\nI will not dally in the Fen; I will gather what information I can and then rejoin you and the alchemist.\\n\\nUntil then, Light be with you, friend.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Sun_p2_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What else do we need?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "All that remains is some token to prove the Grand Vigilant has also answered for his crimes. I believe your friend Galahad knows where to find him.\\n\\nI will go on to Caer Dun and make preparations. See you there, soon, I hope.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Sun_p3_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, just tell me what to do.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Keep in mind, this isn't an exact science, but whatever bad deeds the Vigil performed here, the worst of them were in the Undercroft.\\n\\nI've anointed the entrance with Pure Azoth Water and placed the Sigils.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Yonas_p7_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, he tried to forge a Heartgem.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Hm. It seems his soul was tormented and perhaps that drove him to make poor decisions. This island eventually makes fools of us all.\\n\\nCome though, speak with the young lady. She has made all kinds of preparations.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Sun_p4_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Indeed. You should stay.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Funny, Yonas said the same, and Galahad's on board. So I think I might allow myself to go along with the flow.\\n\\nSpeaking of, I didn't push you on this before, but something happened to you at the Azoth Tree, didn't it?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Galahad_p7_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You know of the purple-eyed sorceress?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, though I know her by another name, the Corpse Crone of Weaver's Fen. I have doubts about her existence.\\n\\nBut Mayor Pennyfather in Calvary is obsessed; go and hear his account and then meet me on the road to the Fen.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Pennyfather_05",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Just information. Who is the Corpse Crone?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "The Corpse Crone!? Don't say that name so loudly lest she be summoned! She is the true cause of ALL this darkness in Brightwood.\\n\\nIndeed, I have written an account, just there. Read it for yourself,  and know the horrors she wrought.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_Pennyfather_06",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I plan to seek her out, at least.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Be wary then, nosy traveler! Weaver's Fen is a foul territory, ridden with sickness and despair, all the crone's doing, no doubt!\\n\\nI wish you luck though, or perhaps a miracle… you'll need it, I fear.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_MorgenGrave_beauty_correct",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Offer the mirror",
        "NPCResponse": "[You place an offering on the plate.]",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!99B_MSQ_06_GravePuzzle_Beauty",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_MorgenGrave_beauty_incorrect",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Offer the mirror",
        "NPCResponse": "[You place an offering on the plate, but it tumbles back into your hands.]",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!99B_MSQ_06_GravePuzzle_Beauty",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_MorgenGrave_family_correct",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Offer the doll",
        "NPCResponse": "[You place an offering on the plate.]",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!99B_MSQ_06_GravePuzzle_Family",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_MorgenGrave_family_incorrect",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Offer the doll",
        "NPCResponse": "[You place an offering on the plate, but it tumbles back into your hands.]",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!99B_MSQ_06_GravePuzzle_Family",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_MorgenGrave_hunter_correct",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Offer the lucky charm",
        "NPCResponse": "[You place an offering on the plate.]",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!99B_MSQ_06_GravePuzzle_Hunter",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_99B_MorgenGrave_hunter_incorrect",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Offer the lucky charm",
        "NPCResponse": "[You place an offering on the plate, but it tumbles back into your hands.]",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!99B_MSQ_06_GravePuzzle_Hunter",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
